

Devina Rosa Damayanti

Data Engineer



Profile

Name:

Devina Rosa Damayanti

Address:

Klipang Permai Blok H 203, RT 01 RW 23, Semarang City, Central Java, Indonesia

Birthday:

11 May, 2001

Email:

devinarosa9@gmail.com

Contact:

08994521622

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/devin a-rosa-damayanti-925585175/

Website:

devinarosa.github.io

Skills

	95 /100
SQL Programming	337100
	70 /100
Data Visualization	
	80/100
Oracle Database & Applicat	ion
	35/100
Machine Learning	
	70/100
HTML 5	75/100
CSS	
5 1:	95 /100
Reporting	ı
RDBMS like Oracle, MySQL,	

About me

Hi I am Devina and now I freshly graduate from Computer and Network Engineering Study. I've been obsessed in Data. I have experienced in Data Enginering from internship on Yogyakarta using Oracle Database. I'd love to learn a new things, work in team, join course or seminars that can develop myself. I am fast learner, smart, and responsible.

Education

7 Vocational High School Semarang (STM Pembangunan) 4 Years Education Program

Computer & Network Engineering - (2016-2020)

- One of the Top 10 of Techcomfest Competition National, 2018
- Graduated with National Exam 33.95/40.00 , 2019
- TOEIC test , score 585 ,2018
- Internship Certificate, 2020

9 High School Semarang

Highschool Completed - (2013-2016)

- Graduated with National Exam 35.60/40.00
- The First winner in the Loptasika V Pakibra Competition in Central Java

Sendang Mulyo 01 Elementary School Semarang

Elementary School Completed - (2007-2013)

- Graduated with National Exam 27.80/30.00
- The Top 8 of English Olympics
- First Ranking for 6 years

Experience

Volunteer Know-Rangers Knowlej.id

Knowlej.id (2020- Present)

- Became a content writer in volunteer know rangers to support poster making and information dissemination on the Now We Know program
- Collaboration with other volunteer in Indonesia and many of sponshorship to help people who COVID-19 affected



PostgreSQL

Internship Data Engineer

CV Karya Hidup Sentosa (2019-2020)

- Became a Data Engineer, I've responsible in resporting and create new report system for other section in this company.
- Create and manage data using SQL Language for create report
- Maintenance and error resolving Oracle E Bussiness Application
- Manage Database RDBMS like MySQl and Oracle Database
- Help a web programmer to create and maintain query for develop website application

Vice President of Palang Merah Remaja SMKN 7 Semarang (2018-2019)

- Have ability and learn Public Speaking Sklill
- Have ability and learn make a best decision for this organization
- Leadership and social ability

Secretary of Kerohanian Islam

SMKN 7 Semarang(2018-2019)

 Became a secretary, help me to learn how to collect data and correspondence that meaningful and very important for the organization.

Hobby

Writing Reading Learn New Things

Product

Achievement

Certification Skill from Dicoding Academy Indonesia (2020)

Certification that I got:

- Python Basic Certificate
- Website Certificate
- Data Visualization Certificate

Attending Event (2020)

- Self Promotion, Women Techmakers International Women's day Seminars and support by GDG-Semarang, I'm Remarkable
- Automate Boring Stuff Data Science Way, Women Techmakers and support by GDG Jakarta, GDG-Depok
- Transformasi Karyawan ke Working from Home, Dicoding Academy

School Achievements

- Top 10 of Networking Competition, Techcomfest Competition in Politeknik Negeri Semarang
- Build and develop website application, named Stembapost Broadcasting App and being BackEnd Developer using Node JS, Database MySQL and Codeigniter
- TOEIC Test, I got score 585
- CCNA Certification IT Essentials
- Internship Certification

Own Project

- Create Website User Manual for Stembapost Application
- Create Personal Website on devinarosa.github.io
- Create Online Shop and Website Fancy Fashion
- Content Writer Posters to Open Donation for Help Other Who Affected COVID-19







Personal Website



User Manual Website